(Howard:)I'm gonna ask her to marry me.
(Leonard:)Marry you?
What?
Yeah.
(Howard:)I just need to figure out the
right time to pop the question.
(Leonard:)Oh, I'd wait.
No rush, no rush.
(Howard(phone rings):)Oh, great. It's my cousin David
about the ring.
(Howard(phone rings):)Hey, David, what'd you find?
Sure, a half a caret's fine.
(Howard(phone rings):)Her freakishly small hands
make anything look big.
(Howard(phone rings):)It's one of the reasons
I love her.
(Leonard:)Man, he's going
to be blindsided.
(Raj:)I know. It'll be awful.
(Sheldon:)Why are you smiling?
(Leonard:)Yeah, Raj, why?
(Raj:)Uh, a smile means something
different in my country.
(Raj:)You know, tears of joy,
smile of sadness.
(Raj:)India's a goofy place.
(Sheldon:)Oh, I'm back to trains.